<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Darwin</string>

    <string name="wifiandnetwork">Wi-Fi &amp; Network</string>
    <string name="timeanddate">Time &amp; Date</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="demoScenes">Demo Scenes</string>
    <string name="no_devices">It looks like you do not have any devices in room.</string>
    <string name="no_rooms">It looks like you do not have any rooms added.</string>


    <!--watch request strings-->
    <string name="access_request">Request from watch for access app</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>

    <!--pin enter screen-->
    <string name="pin_enter_screen_title">Enter Pin Here</string>
    <string name="new_pin_enter_screen_title">Enter New Pin Here</string>
    <string name="pin_enter_valid_pin">Enter valid pin</string>
    <string name="store_btn">Save</string>


    <string name="on">All on</string>
    <string name="off">All off</string>

    <string name="turn_on_off_pin">Turn ON/OFF PIN</string>
    <string name="turn_on_pin">Turn ON Access PIN</string>
    <string name="turn_off_pin">Turn OFF Access PIN</string>



    <!--about fragment strings-->
    <string name="about_darwin_id">DARWIN ID</string>
    <string name="about_reboot_darwin">Reboot DARWIN</string>
    <string name="about_darwin_firmware_version">DARWIN Firmware Version</string>
    <string name="about_app_version">App Version</string>


    <string name="no_experiences">It looks like you don\'t have any experience</string>
    <string name="no_experiences1">added in favorite</string>
    <string name="no_elements">It looks like you don\'t have any elements </string>
    <string name="no_elements1">added in favorite</string>
    <string name="hub_softrest"> Darwin is soft reset</string>
    <string name="upgradepackage_msg">Please upgrade your package to use this feature</string>


    <string name="after_login_emit_text">Authenticating...</string>
    <string name="re_login">Some thing is wrong,Please login again.</string>
    <string name="after_login_reponce_text">Getting DARWIN...</string>
    <string name="after_hub_ip_connect_text">Connecting to DARWIN</string>
    <string name="multi_signup_connect">Authenticate connecting...</string>
    <string name="multi_signup_emit">Sign up with multiple hub...</string>

    <string name="signup_in_progress">Sign up in progress..</string>
    <string name="play_song_text">No Playlist is selected</string>
    <string name="network_change_to_connect">Please change network,to get darwin you have to connect </string>
    <string name="network_change_str">Please change network,to get darwin.</string>


    <string name="fetch_data_after_ip_connect">Fetching DARWIN data...</string>
    <string name="hub_scanning">DARWIN Scanning...</string>
    <string name="check_user">Checking DARWIN user...</string>
    <string name="hub_offline">DARWIN is Offline Try again</string>
    <string name="authentication">Authentication...</string>
    <string name="trying_to_connect">Connecting to DARWIN</string>
    <string name="internet_issue">Internet Connectivity Error</string>
    <string name="network_issue">Network Connectivity Error</string>
    <string name="server_issue">Server Connectivity Error</string>
    <string name="tech_user">The user does not have login access to the Application</string>


    /*******activities scene title********/


    <string name="activites_cooking">Cooking</string>
    <string name="activites_circadian_demo">Circadian Demo</string>
    <string name="activites_relax">Relax</string>
    <string name="activites_energise">Energise</string>
    <string name="activites_prepare">Prepare for Sleep</string>
    <string name="activites_comfort">Darwin Comfort</string>
    <string name="activites_ambiance">An ambiance designed to help you to feel\n more </string>

    /***** climate dialog string****/
    <string name="purification_dialog_off_title">Turn off Purification?</string>
    <string name="comfort_band_diff_disc">Comfort band cannot be less than 3 degrees.</string>
    <string name="purification_dialog_on_title">Turn on Purification?</string>
    <string name="purification_off_state">TURN OFF PURIFICATION</string>
    <string name="air_purification_title">Air Purification</string>
    <string name="thermostat_auto_mode">Your heating and cooling will be turned off, but</string>
    <string name="thermostat_heat_mode">Your System will be turned off, but</string>
    <string name="thermostate_heating_mode">Your heating  will be turned off, but</string>
    <string name="thermostate_cooling_mode">Your cooling  will be turned off, but</string>
    <string name="purification_dialog_off_desc">You are about to turn off Purification and Climate\n control. Are you sure you want to do this?</string>
    <string name="purification_dialog_off_desc_mob">You are about to turn off\n Purification and Climate control. \nAre you sure you want to do this?</string>
    <string name="purification_dialog_on_desc">You are about to turn on Purification and Climate\n control. Are you sure you want to do this?</string>
    <string name="purification_dialog_on_desc_mob">You are about to turn on\n Purification and Climate control.\n Are you sure you want to do this?</string>


    <string name="song_title">Song title</string>
    <string name="allow_water_notification">Allow Water Filter Notification</string>
    <string name="allow_air_notification">Allow Air Filter Notification</string>
    <string name="cooking_scene">Cooking</string>
    <string name="kitchen_only">Kitchen Only</string>
    <string name="unable_to_connect">Unable to connect.</string>

    <string name="user_id">User ID</string>
    <string name="time_zone">The Time settings of your device does not match with the DARWIN Time settings.Please check the Date,Time and Timezone settings and Try again</string>
    <string name="hub_version_not_match">Hub version not match please update hub.</string>
    <string name="artist_name">Artist name</string>
    <string name="valid_match_pass">Password not match</string>
    <string name="incorrect_user_pass">Username or Password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="empty_user_id">User ID cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="empty_email_id">Email ID cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="password_short">Password is too short.</string>
    <string name="password_long">Password is too long.</string>
    <string name="empty_password">Password cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="valid_user_id">Please enter valid User ID.</string>
    <string name="valid_email_id">Please enter valid Email ID.</string>
    <string name="valid_recovery_id">Please enter valid recovery mail ID.</string>
    <string name="empty_recovery_mail">Recovery mail ID cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="valid_re_password">Re-enter password</string>
    <string name="valid_serial_name">Enter darwin id</string>
    <string name="valid_first_name">Enter first name</string>
    <string name="valid_last_name">Enter last name</string>
    <string name="fav_place_holder_title">Hmm, it looks like you don\'t </string>
    <string name="dawn_is_running">Do you want to deactivate the current dawn simulation?</string>
    <string name="sleep_is_running">Do you want to deactivate the current sleep simulation?</string>
    <string name="prepare_for_sleep_is_running">Your Prepare for Sleep scene is currently active do you want to deactivate?</string>
    <string name="thermostat_place_holder_desc">Your heating and cooling will be turned off, but </string>
    <string name="current_action"><u>Current Actions</u></string>
    <string name="fav_place_holder_desc1">    </string>
    <string name="save_location">Saving Location</string>


    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>

    <string name="domain">\u0040darwin.com</string>
    <string name="register_succeful">REGISTERED SUCCESSFULLY...</string>


    <string name="favorites_text">Favorites</string>

    <!-- room devices-->
    <string name="energise">Energise</string>

    <string name="music">Music</string>

    <!--more tab-->
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>

    <!-- support-->

    <string name="darwing_installtion_msg">DARWIN Installation/Update is in progress.</string>
    <string name="circadian_trigger_msg">Synchronizing Your Home to Your Circadian Rhythm</string>
    <string name="desiretemperature">DESIRED TEMPERATURE</string>

    <string name="prompt_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="new_account">Don’t have an account?  Sign up</string>
    <string name="action_sign_fb">SIGN UP OR LOGIN WITH FACEBOOK</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->


    <string-array name="SSId">
        <item>No SSID available</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="notify_name">
        <item>Alan Charles</item>
        <item>Mike Howard</item>
        <item>James Bond</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ip_type">
        <item>Select Connection</item>
        <item>Static</item>
        <item>DHCP</item>

    </string-array>
    <string name="notifier_title">Please select notifier name</string>

    <string name="installationdate">Installation Date</string>
    <string name="installationdateformat">DD/MM/YYYY</string>
    <string name="selectroom">Please Select Room</string>
    <string name="selectzone">Please Select Zone</string>
    <string name="selectscence">Please Select Scenes</string>
    <string name="darwin_id">Darwin ID</string>
    <string name="LocationGPS">To continue, let your device turn on location.</string>
    <string name="Location">Location(GPS)</string>
    <string name="Settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Cancel">Cancel</string>


    <string name="google_maps_key" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">AIzaSyB4ic5JmSLcYwdAZA0R2wIw06aoOccu2Bo </string>

    <!-- TODO: remove this placeholder text -->

    <string name="no_profile_setting">No profile setting available</string>
    <string name="recovery_email">Recovery Email ID </string>
    <string name="hub_loss">is not on network.</string>
    <string name="tvoc">Volatile organic compounds (VOCs) are a group of chemicals emitted as gases, that easily evaporate at room
temperature. Levels of VOC’s are up to 10 x higher indoors and many household items emit VOC’s including paint,
glues, solvents, cleaning products, air fresheners, aerosol sprays and pesticides. VOC’s are associated with short and
long-term adverse health effects such as eye, nose and throat irritation, headaches, nausea, skin allergies, fatigue
and possible organ damage.</string>

    <string name="co_pollutant">Carbon Monoxide (CO) is a by-product of combustion, and is an odourless, tasteless and colourless gas. Common household sources include gas cooking and heating appliances, wood or charcoal fireplaces and barbeques, vehicle exhaust and cigarette smoke. Inhalation of CO can cause illness and even death, as it deprives the blood of oxygen.Symptoms include headache, malaise, nausea, dizziness or flu-like signs without fever.</string>

    <string name="co2_pollutant">Carbon Dioxide (CO₂) is a colorless, odorless gas that is naturally present in air and is produced by respiration and burning carbon. Elevated levels of CO₂ indoors, typically caused by a high density of people and insufficient ventilation, can lead to drowsiness and reduced cognitive performance. </string>
    <string name="no_pollutant">Nitrogen dioxide (NO₂) is a significant air pollutant often caused by motor vehicle exhaust, unflued gas heaters and the burning of fossil fuels, coal, oil and gas. Exposure to NO₂ over short periods can aggravate allergies and respiratory problems, particularly asthma and cause coughing, wheezing or difficulty breathing. Children and the
elderly are generally at a greater risk of the health effects of NO₂.</string>
    <string name="o_pollutant">Ozone is naturally occurring in the atmosphere, and a common component of urban smog which can damage crops, trees and other vegetation. Exposure to elevated levels of Ozone may cause symptoms including eye,
nose and throat irritation, respiratory or cardiac symptoms like shortness of breath, chest pain, and wheezing.  </string>
    <string name="pm2_pollutant">Particulate matter (PM) consist of airborne solid or liquid particles. PM ₂.₅ are fine inhalable particulates with a diameter 2.5 micrometres or smaller. Common sources are vehicle emissions, tobacco and open fire smoke, cooking and burning of fragrant candles and oils. PM ₂.₅  particulates can cause irritation of the eyes, nose and throat, also exacerbate medical conditions such as asthma, cardiovascular disease and chronic respiratory illness.</string>
    <string name="pm10_pollutant">Particulate matter (PM) consist of airborne solid or liquid particles. Common sources of PM ₁₀ particles include household dust and dander, pollen, mould spores, aerosol spray, tobacco and wood fire smoke and vehicle exhaust.The composition of particulate matter varies with place, season and weather conditions. PM ₁₀ particles tend to affect
the upper respiratory tract – eyes, sinus and throat and can worsen allergies, asthma, heart and lung conditions. </string>
    <string name="so_pollutant">Sulphur Dioxide (SO₂) found in the atmosphere is primarily released by the combustion of fossil fuels from industrial facilities, smelting of mineral ores and emissions from heavy machinery. Exposure to SO₂ can cause symptoms such as sneezing, wheezing, shortness of breath, chest tightness and irritated airways. Children, the
elderly and sensitive individuals are particularly reactive to SO₂.</string>


    <string name="privacy">
        PRIVACY POLICY
Delos Welltek Australia (“Delos,” “we,” “us,” or “our”), is committed to protecting your
privacy and the data on the DARWINTM app (the “DARWIN app”). To demonstrate this
commitment, we have adopted this privacy policy (this “Policy”). The Policy is designed to
help you understand generally how the DARWIN app collects, uses or discloses
information about you. Your use of the DARWIN app is subject to this Policy and our Terms
of Use; by accessing the DARWIN app you acknowledge and agree to accept this Policy,
which we may amend at any time. If we update this Policy, we will post the updated Policy
here. Any such changes will be effective upon posting. You should consult the “Privacy
Policy” on the DARWIN app periodically.
The DARWIN Ecosystem is a wellness intelligence platform incorporating science-based
technologies and solutions designed to enhance physical and emotional well-being in
homes. DARWIN creates and maintains the natural environment in your home that is
essential for enhanced health, wellbeing and performance. Based on the learnings gained
from over 7 years with the foremost medical and scientific institutions in the world, the
DARWIN platform monitors the health of your home to meet the needs of occupants

I. NOTICE OF OUR POLICY
This Policy tells you, among other things, what information we gather from you and why,
how we may use or disclose that information, and how you can update your information.
Please read this Policy carefully, and feel free to contact us at privacy.dwa@delos.com.au
if you have questions about this Policy or if you would like to update information you have
provided to us.
Please note that this Policy applies only to the DARWIN app, and not to any other
application or website linked to the DARWIN app, including any social media websites
linked to the DARWIN app, or any other interaction with Welltek. We do not control the
privacy policies or practices of others. We encourage you to ask questions and read the
privacy policies of other websites and application before you disclose any personal
information to them.

II. WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION ARE COLLECTED AND WHY?
Welltek may collect personally identifiable information or non-personally identifiable
information through your use of the DARWIN app. Personally identifiable information (or
personal information) is information that personally identifies you, such as your name,
postal address and email address, and non-personally identifiable information is
information that does not personally identify you, including anonymous information and
aggregated data about users of the DARWIN app. Information is collected in order to
provide services to you, tailor services to you based on your preferences and display
information to you about the environment inside your home, as well as to improve our
services and offerings and for other general research purposes. Information can be
collected if you submit it to us or it may be collected automatically through technology. The
DARWIN app uses information it collects in order to recognize and identify the property,
sensors and other appliances and products in your home, and collect data generated from
those sensors and other appliances and products. We also may use your personal
information to respond to your requests and provide support, to communicate with you, toprovide updates to you about relevant products and services, and otherwise provide our
products and services to you.

a. Information submitted by you
You may submit information to us when you use the DARWIN app. For
instance, you may submit information in order to authenticate your credentials
and input your preferences including your name, email address, social
connection (single sign on user option), log-in and password credentials
created by you, additional users that may access the DARWIN app, your
preferences, your favorites, your schedule, and other information you provide
to help us customize our services for you and optimize system performance.

b. Location Information
You may submit location information, including your time zone and address, in
your preferences and certain location information may be collected
automatically by using the DARWIN app such as Internet Protocol address,
street address (including city, state, territory and postcode), and the products
and appliances in your home compatible with the DARWIN app. Time zone
and location data is used to customize settings in your home, such as triggering
dawn simulation and controlling other lighting timers. By registering and using
the DARWIN app, you consent to such collection and use of this information.

c. Device and environmental information collected automatically
The DARWIN app recognizes devices in your home that you choose to connect
to the DARWIN app and collects information about those devices to display the
information to you so that you can better understand the environment inside
your home. Whenever you select to activate devices via the DARWIN app, we
automatically receive and record information on our servers, logs and
databases from the DARWIN app or device(s). In particular, the DARWIN app
is designed to allow you to connect various devices you choose to connect in
your home (for example your lighting, HVAC system, and/or water filter) to the
DARWIN app. While connected to the DARWIN app, these devices
automatically report information to our servers, logs and databases (including
information you may have provided when setting up the devices or the
DARWIN app). For instance, if you connect an indoor environmental quality
(“IEQ”) sensor to the DARWIN app and activate the IEQ portion of the DARWIN
app, the IEQ data (along with other information such as applicable room,
device name and location) will be transmitted and displayed to you via the
DARWIN app. Specifically, your home contains sensors to help you monitor
the environment in your home. Some information the DARWIN app collects
from your sensors and displays for you on the DARWIN app if you activate this
feature include temperature, relative humidity and air quality conditions, such
as Particulate Matter 10, Particulate Matter 2.5, carbon dioxide, total volatile
organic compounds, temperature and humidity.

d. Use of Non-personal information and aggregated dataThe DARWIN app collects data about your use of the DARWIN app such as
commands triggered and other DARWIN app usage metrics. Welltek may use
non-personally identifiable information and anonymized, aggregated data to
understand better how the DARWIN app is used, including average time spent
using the DARWIN app and pages viewed, to provide users with customized
services and information, and to gather other relevant statistics and
information. Welltek collects this information to measure the use of the
DARWIN app and to improve the content of the DARWIN app. Such
information, and other information we derive from an individual user’s
information, supports our continued research, and allows us to continue to
grow and improve our services and products.

e. Information collected by technology
Welltek and its agents use technologies like cookies to help you use our
services more easily and help us continuously improve the DARWIN app and
our services. Personal and non-personal information that may be collected
using such technologies may include IP addresses, time spent on the DARWIN
app, location information and a user’s internet service provider. A “cookie” is a
small data file that a website can send to your browser, which may then be
stored on your hard drive to help the website “remember” information about
you when you return to the website, such as your preferences for the website
or account identifications. We use simple session based cookies for logged in
users on the website linked to the DARWIN app to track active sessions. You
may have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies; however, doing
so may affect the performance of the DARWIN app or restrict the way in which
we may provide our services to you.


III. HOW DOES WELLTEK DISCLOSE MY INFORMATION?
We may share non-personal and aggregated information we collect from the DARWIN
app in a manner permitted by law including to our affiliates and other companies with
whom we conduct business.
We may disclose your personal information to our affiliates and other entities and
individuals we engage to perform functions on our behalf and to help us to operate the
DARWIN app and our business and deliver our services to you, or we may disclose
information if you consent to such disclosure. Some of these other entities and individuals
may include technology and other consultants, attorneys, accountants, clerical staff,
website or database hosting companies, service and technical support companies,
analytics companies, e-commerce providers and financial institutions (for the purpose of
processing credit card transactions in the event you make a purchase from the DARWIN
app). These entities and individuals will have access to your personal information to the
extent necessary to perform services on our behalf. Some of these service providers may
be located outside of Australia, including DARWIN app and user data stored by our third-
party hosting provider International Business Machines, Inc. in a data center located in the
United States, customer information used to provide you customer support stored on third
party platform Zendesk with data centers that may be located in the United States or
European Economic Area. Moreover, certain data may be shared with our third party
technical team Clouds Inc. located in India when a support ticket is generated.We may also disclose your personal information if legally required to do so, if requested
to do so by a government entity, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary
to conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process, protect the rights or
property of Welltek, prevent a crime, or protect the integrity of the DARWIN app and
personal safety of our users or the public.
We may also disclose and transfer your personal information to a third party who acquires
any or all of our assets, whether by way of acquisition, merger, consolidation, or purchase
of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event Welltek becomes the
subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, Welltek or its
liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license, or otherwise
dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court.

IV. HOW CAN I OPT-OUT OF RECEIVING EMAIL COMMUNICATION?
We may email you in order to notify you of changes or offer you services we think you may
be interested in. We will not send unsolicited messages to you if you indicate that you do
not wish to receive such messages. However, if you, as a user, do not want your personal
information used as otherwise detailed in this Policy, then you must not use the DARWIN
app.

V. SECURITY
The security of your information is important to us, and we endeavor to protect your
personal information. However, there is no such thing as perfect security on the Internet,
and you provide personal information to us at your own risk. Welltek expressly disclaims
all liability for any damages, losses or claims of any kind relating to any personal
information that you provide to us or others through the DARWIN app. When you use the
DARWIN app, we encourage you to protect your information and use precautions,
including but not limited to, using strong passwords and not sharing your password and
account information with any other person.

VI.
INFORMATION REGARDING CHILDREN
This DARWIN app is not directed to children (persons under 15 years of age), and Welltek
does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. If a child under 15 has
provided personally identifiable information to us through the DARWIN app, a parent or
guardian may inform us at the address for notices below, and we will use commercially
reasonable efforts to delete it from our database, subject to applicable law and this Policy.

VII. HOW CAN I UPDATE MY INFORMATION, ASK A QUESTION OR ISSUE A
COMPLAINT?
You can always update your account information or correct information you provided
through profile settings in the DARWIN app, and if you require further assistance, please
visit delos.com.au/support. To ask any questions or submit a complaint about this Policy
and information handling, please contact us at privacy.dwa@delos.com.au,1-3000-
DELOS.
Last Updated: August 15, 2018


TERMS OF USE
Thank you for using the DARWIN app (the “DARWIN app”). These Terms of Use along
with the Privacy Policy] incorporated herein govern your use of the DARWIN app and the
content, features, information and services made available on and through the DARWIN
app. Please read these Terms of Use carefully before using the DARWIN app or any
services offered on the DARWIN app. These Terms of Use, when agreed to by you, will
form a binding agreement between you and Delos Welltek Australia (collectively "Welltek",
"we", "us", "our", and other similar pronouns).
1. Acceptance of Terms of Use. Your use of the DARWIN app indicates your acceptance
of these Terms of Use. If you do not accept these Terms of Use, do not use the DARWIN
app. From time to time these Terms of Use may be revised and will be included in the
DARWIN app. Please review these Terms of Use from time to time. Your continued use
of the DARWIN app will constitute your agreement to the most current version of these
Terms of Use. If at any time you do not agree to these Terms of Use, do not use the
DARWIN app.
2. Contact. For questions concerning the use of the DARWIN app and its services, please
visit delos.com.au/support or send an email to privacy.dwa@delos.com.au.
3. License; Intellectual Property Rights. Welltek grants you a revocable, non-exclusive,
non-transferable, limited license to download, install and use the DARWIN app solely for
your personal, non-commercial purposes strictly in accordance with these Terms of Use.
All text, graphics, design, and programming on the DARWIN app (“Content”) is the sole
property of Welltek or their respective owners and are protected by copyright law,
trademark law and international treaties. Welltek authorizes you to view a single copy of
the Content on the DARWIN app solely for your personal, noncommercial use. You may
not reproduce, modify, display, sell, or distribute the Content, or use it in any other way for
public or commercial purpose.
The "look" and "feel" of the DARWIN app (including color combinations, layout, design
and all other graphical elements) are also protected by copyright law, trademark law and
international treaties. All product names, names of services, trademarks and service
marks (the “Marks”) are the property of Welltek or the property of their respective owners.
You may not use the Marks for any purpose whatsoever other than as permitted by these
Terms of Use. Nothing contained in these Terms of Use is intended to confer upon or
assign to you any right, claim, title or interest in or to any of Welltek’s intellectual property
and proprietary rights.
4. Acceptable Use of the DARWIN app. The DARWIN app may be used within the
context of the products, services and information contained in the DARWIN app. The
information displayed in the DARWIN app may not be used for any purpose except in
connection with your personal, direct use of the DARWIN app as permitted by these Terms
of Use, and may not be excerpted, summarized, duplicated or otherwise removed from
the DARWIN app. In addition, you represent, warrant and agree that you will not use (or
plan, encourage or help others to use) the DARWIN app for any purpose or in any manner
that is prohibited by these Terms of Use or by applicable law. As a condition of your use
of the DARWIN app, you promise not to use the DARWIN app or related services in any
manner prohibited by applicable law and regulations. By way of example and not as alimitation, you shall not and shall not permit any third party to either (a) take any action or
(b) upload, download, post, submit or otherwise distribute or facilitate distribution of any
content on or through the DARWIN app, including without limitation any user submission,
that:
• infringes any intellectual property or other proprietary right of any other person or entity
or violates any law or contractual duty;
•you know is false, misleading, untruthful or inaccurate;
•is unlawful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, libelous, deceptive,
fraudulent, invasive of another\'s privacy, tortious or obscene;
•constitutes unauthorized or unsolicited advertising, junk or bulk e-mail ("spamming");
•involves commercial activities (whether or not for profit) and/or sales without Welltek’s
prior written consent, such as contests, sweepstakes, barter, advertising, or pyramid
schemes;
•violates Welltek’s posted privacy, DARWIN app or other policies.






You shall not (directly or indirectly):
• interfere with the proper operation of the DARWIN app, including, but not limited to, by
attacking, hacking into, or otherwise attempting to penetrate any non-publicly
accessible elements of the DARWIN app, through the use of bots, trojan horses,
viruses, DNS attacks, or other technology which is designed or intended to interfere
with the proper operation of the DARWIN app or the use of the DARWIN app by users.
• alter or modify the Content or remove our copyright notice or other legends.
• use manual or automated software, devices, or other processes to "crawl" or "spider"
any page of the DARWIN app; or
• harvest or scrape any Content from the DARWIN app; or attempt to interfere with
service to any users of the DARWIN app, host or network, including, without limitation,
via means of submitting malware to the DARWIN app.

5. Monitoring of Information. Welltek does not assume any obligation to review the
accuracy, completeness, truthfulness or content of any information submitted to the
DARWIN app. Welltek reserves the right to suspend your use of the DARWIN app for any
reason at any time, in its sole discretion.

6. Rights to Information. We may use information and content submitted by you or
collected on an aggregated basis related to your use of the DARWIN app in a number of
ways to provide our services as further described in our Privacy Policy. You hereby grant
to Welltek a non-exclusive, irrevocable, perpetual, worldwide, fully paid, royalty-free,
sublicensable and transferable right and license to use, copy, edit, modify, reproduce,
distribute, prepare derivative works of, publicly display, publicly perform, and otherwise
fully exploit non-identifying information submitted in connection with the DARWIN app, the
services and Welltek’s (and its successors\' and assigns) business, including without
limitation for promoting and redistributing part or all of the DARWIN app (and derivative
works thereof) or the services in any media formats and through any media channels
(including, without limitation, third party website and feeds). For clarity, the foregoing
license grant to Welltek does not affect your other ownership or license rights in your
information, including the right to grant additional licenses to the material in your
information submission(s), unless otherwise agreed in writing with Welltek.

7. Passwords and Log-in information. To help protect the security of the DARWIN app
and your information, you should follow security best practices such as protecting your
user name and password. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your
user name and password, and you are responsible for all uses of your account and
registration, whether or not authorized by you. Do not share your user name or password
with any other person. In the event you become aware of misuse or unauthorized use of
your password, it is your obligation to notify Welltek. Welltek shall have no responsibility
for loss or misused user names or passwords or for unauthorized access.

8. Termination of Access to DARWIN app. Users who violate these Terms of Use may
be denied access to the DARWIN app at the sole discretion of Welltek.

9. Disclaimer of Warranties, Indemnification and Limitations of Liability. Your
agreement to the following disclaimers and limitations are a material inducement to
Welltek to permit you to access and use the DARWIN app.

Your use of the DARWIN app,
and the obligations and liabilities of Welltek in respect to your use of the DARWIN app, is
expressly limited as follows:
Conduct of Users.
Welltek assumes no responsibility for the activities or conduct
of users.
Third Party Information or DARWIN app. The DARWIN app may display the
content, services, products and/or hyperlinks of other companies or persons.
Notwithstanding the presentation of any third-party information on the DARWIN app, no
such presentation shall be considered an endorsement, representation or warranty, either
express or implied, by Welltek on behalf of any third party. Welltek shall have no liability
or responsibility whatsoever for the content, subject matter or substance of any information
accessed or obtained from third party applications accessed from the DARWIN app. We
encourage you to review the applicable terms of use and privacy policies of such third-
party applications. Functionality may depend upon functionality of third-party applications
and use of the DARWIN app in conjunction with third party applications. It is not required
that you download third-party applications but functionality may be affected if you do not
download such third-party content. For instance, while you are not required to download
the Sonos application, if you do not do so, then audio functionality of the DARWIN app
may be limited. Qmotion and Flic applications are other examples of third-party
applications that should be installed as part of your initial setup if you choose those
products.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES. THE DARWIN APP AND CONTENT MADE
AVALABLE ON THE DARWIN APP ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND “AS
AVAILABLE” BASIS AND WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OR REPRESENTATION OF ANY
KIND. WELLTEK DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL EXPRESS AND IMPLIED WARRANTIES
WHATSOEVER AS TO THE DARWIN APP OR CONTENT MADE AVAILABLE ON THE
DARWIN APP, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTIES’ RIGHTS,
LOSS OF DATA, FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AVAILAIBLITY, SECURITY,
ACCURACY, FREEDOM FROM VIRUSES OR MALWARE, COMPLETENESS,
TIMELINESS, FUNCTIONALITY, RELIABILITY, SEQUENCING OR SPEED OF
DELIVERY.WELLTEK’S ACTIVITIES AND SERVICES ARE INTENDED TO HELP SUPPORT YOUR
HEALTH AND WELL-BEING.
HOWEVER, PLEASE BE AWARE THAT AN
INDIVIDUAL’S HEALTH AND WELL-BEING ARE DETERMINED BY A NUMBER OF
FACTORS PARTICULAR TO THAT INDIVIDUAL, OTHER THAN THAT INDIVIDUAL’S
CURRENT ENVIRONMENT. THESE FACTORS INCLUDE BUT ARE NOT LIMITED TO,
PERSONAL CURRENT AND PAST CONDUCT, GENETICS, FAMILY HISTORY, AND
PSYCHOLOGICAL FACTORS. WELLTEK IS NOT A LICENSED HEALTHCARE
PROVIDER, AND MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES THAT ANY OF
ITS SERVICES OR RECOMMENDATIONS, OR ANY PRODUCTS SOLD OR
RECOMMENDED, WILL CURE ANY ILLNESSESS OR DISEASES, IMPROVE THE
OVERALL HEALTH OR WELL-BEING OF ANY SPECIFIC INDIVIDUAL(S), OR CAUSE
A SPACE TO BE FREE FROM BACTERIA, VIRUSES, ALLERGENS, VOLATILE
ORGANIC COMPOUNDS, OR OTHER PATHOGENS. MOREOVER, WELLTEK MAKES
NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES THAT THE PRODUCTS OR
APPROACHES IT RECOMMENDS ARE EXHAUSTIVE OF ALL AVAILABLE
ALTERNATIVES. WELLTEK (FOR PURPOSES OF THIS PARAGRAPH, EITHER
ITSELF AND/OR THROUGH ONE OR MORE OF ITS AFFILIATES) INVESTS IN, OWNS,
AND/OR INTERNALLY DEVELOPS CERTAIN OF THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES
THAT IT RECOMMENDS. WELLTEK AND ITS AFFILIATES ALSO MAINTAIN
DISTRIBUTION AND OTHER CONTRACTUAL ARRANGEMENTS WITH THIRD PARTY
PROVIDERS OF SUCH PRODUCTS AND SERVICES. THEREFORE, WELLTEK MAY
BENEFIT COMMERCIALLY FROM THE SALE OR PROVISION OF THESE PRODUCTS
AND SERVICES. NEITHER WELLTEK’S SERVICES NOR THE INFORMATION
DISPLAYED ON THE DARWIN APP OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU CONSTITUTE
THE PRACTICE OF MEDICINE OR THE PROVISION OF ANY PROFESSIONAL
HEALTHCARE SERVICES, DIAGNOSIS OR TREATMENT, AND NOTHING
DISPLAYED ON THE DARWIN APP OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU SHOULD BE
CONSIDERED, OR USED AS A SUBSTITUTE FOR, MEDICAL ADVICE, DIAGNOSIS
OR TREATMENT.
FURTHERMORE, WELLTEK MAKES NO WARRANTIES THAT THE PRODUCTS AND
MATERIALS RECOMMENDED BY IT OR CONNECTED TO THE DARWIN APP WILL
NOT AFFECT PEOPLE WITH ALLERGIES OR PROPENSITIES FOR OTHER ADVERSE
REACTIONS, AND WELLTEK ASSUMES NO LIABILITY FOR ALLERGIC OR OTHER
ADVERSE REACTIONS TO PRODUCTS OR MATERIALS MENTIONED,
RECOMMENDED AND/OR SOLD ON, OR CONNECTED TO, THE DARWIN APP.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. IN NO EVENT SHALL WELLTEK OR ITS
AFFILIATES BE LIABLE FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT,
SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, (INCLUDING LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF
GOODWILL, PERSONAL OR PROPERTY DAMAGE), WHETHER BASED ON
WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER
OR NOT WELLTEK IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
Indemnification. You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless WELLTEK
and its affiliates and its and their employees, officers, directors and investors harmless
from and against any and all liability, claims, causes of actions, damages, costs and
expenses, including but not limited to, attorneys’ fees and costs of suit, arising out of your
breach of these Terms of Use.10. General. These Terms of Use are governed by the internal substantive laws of
Australia, without respect to its conflict of laws principles. Jurisdiction for any claims arising
under these Terms of Use shall lie exclusively with the courts within Australia. If any
provision of these Terms of Use is found to be invalid by any court having competent
jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining
provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. The failure of
Welltek to enforce any term or condition of these Terms of Use shall not be deemed a
waiver thereof and shall not prevent its later enforcement.
Last Updated: August 15, 2018
    </string>

</resources>